We loaded in our data,
我们加载了数据
and here's my first solution for calculating the percentage of fraudulent data.
这是第一个任务“计算欺诈性数据的百分比”的实现方式
First, from our transaction dataframe,
首先从 transaction_df 中
I'm counting up the occurrences of data points in each class using.value_counts.
使用 .value_counts 计算每个类别中的数据点出现次数
This gives me back an array of counts.
返回一个计数数组
I can get the fraudulent counts from counts[1] and the valid counts from counts[0].
可以从 counts[1] 获得欺诈性数据点计数 并从 counts[0] 获得有效性数据点计数
Then, to get the fraction that I want,
欺诈性数据的百分比等于
I just divide the fraudulent count by the total count here.
欺诈性计数除以总计数
Then, I'm returning that fraudulent percentage and running my test cell below.
然后返回 fraudulent_percentage
I can see that out of about 285,000 data points,
可以看出 在约 285,000 个数据点中
about 500 are fraudulent which makes up about 0.17 percent of the data.
有约 500 个欺诈性数据点 百分比约为 0.17%
So this is not even a whole percent that's labeled as fraudulent.
甚至不到 1%
Now, on the one hand, this is good.
一方面 对于此人来说 这是好事
We don't want this person to have experienced many fraudulent transactions,
我们不希望他多次遇到欺诈性交易
but it will be challenging data to learn from.
但是对于机器学习来说就比较麻烦
Many algorithms assume that we have
很多算法认为
a relatively even distribution of data among the classes.
我们的数据在各个类别之间的分布是相对均匀的
We'll get into ways to manage a class imbalance like this later on.
稍后我们将介绍如何处理这种类别不平衡性
Next, I wanted to split this data into a training set and test set for evaluation later.
接着将此数据拆分为训练集和测试集 之后使用测试集评估模型
So here's my solution for splitting the data according to a past in train_frac.
下面说说我是如何根据传入的 train_frac 拆分数据的
First, I'm grabbing my dataframe of transaction data
首先获取交易数据 dataframe
and converting it into a matrix using df.as_matrix.
并通过 df.as_matrix 将数据转换为矩阵
This will make it easier for me to use Numpy functions to shuffle and split this data.
这样便于使用 Numpy 函数随机重排和拆分数据
Next, according to my past in random seed,
接着 根据传入的随机 seed
I'm randomly shuffling all of the data in this matrix.
随机重排该矩阵中的所有数据
Here, I'm getting the train size,
设置 train_size
the amount of training data that I want to keep.
表示训练数据的量
This is going to be the number of rows of data in
等于矩阵中的行数乘以
our matrix times the train fraction that's passed in.
传入的 train_frac
Since this fraction is a decimal value,
这个分数是一个小数值
I'll actually want to cast this to be an integer type.
需要转型为整型
So I'm casting it to an int because our data is discrete,
因为我们的数据是离散的
that is I can't have half a datapoint.
不能有一半的数据点
So this is going to round down
它会向下舍入任何浮点值
any float value and this is okay behavior for such a division.
对于拆分数据来说 这么做没问题
Now, these train size will be the index of
train_size 将为
the row that I want to split my matrix data at.
拆分矩阵数据的索引位置
So here, I'm getting my train features up until that index, train size.
训练特征为直到索引 train_size 前的特征
I know my class labels are in the last column of the dataframe,
我知道类别标签在 dataframe 的最后一列
so I am not including that in the features here with negative one,
-1 表示不包含
not the last column.
最后一列
Then, here, I am getting that last value to save as my class labels.
然后在这里将最后一个值保存为类别标签
Then, I'm doing something similar with the test features and labels.
测试特征和标签也相似
I'm getting the remaining rows of data.
获取剩余的数据行
Notice the placement of train size before the colon, here, and after,
注意 这里是 train_size 在冒号前面
here, and then, here,
这里是在冒号后面
getting the last column of test labels.
然后在这里获取最后的测试标签列
Finally, I'm just returning all of these in a specified return order,
最后 以特定的返回顺序返回这些值
training features and labels,
训练特征和标签
and test features and labels in separate tuples.
然后是测试特征和标签 它们是单独的元组
So this completes my function.
这样就完成了这个函数
Now, I can call this function in the next cell and test out the shape.
在下个单元格中调用该函数并测试形状
I'm leaving a default split of 0.7 for
拆分比例是默认的 7:3 比例
my training data so 30 percent of my data should go to test data.
70% 是训练数据 30% 是测试数据
Then, I have a few tests down here that check that I have the correct shape for each of
下面有几个测试部分 检查每个特征的形状是否正确
these features and that all my labels are indeed zeros and ones.
以及标签是否的确为 0 和 1
This cell prints up the number of training points that I generated,
这个单元格会输出训练数据点的数量
about 200,000, the number of test points,
约为 200,000 然后是测试数据点的数量
and a test first item and label.
然后测试下第一项及其标签
I should see 30 features in this first item and a single class label.
第一项应该有 30 个特征 并且有一个类别标签
Zero indicates a valid transaction.
0 表示有效交易
So now that we have our train data and test data,
我们已经有了训练数据和测试数据
these are almost ready to be fed into a model.
这些数据差不多可以传入模型中了
So next, I'll outline how to build and train a binary classification model.
接下来 我将介绍如何构建和训练二元分类模型